I went to Australia. Has anybody ever
been to YOU'VE BEEN TO AUSTRALIA? OH MY
AUSTRALIA IS AMAZING. They have pink
SAND BEACHES. WOO!
>> [screaming]
>> YOU GET OUT THERE IT'S LIKE A CLOUD,
BABY. YOU BE LIKE WOO
>> [laughter]
>> OOH, when I get to Australia, that's how
I swim.
Oh yes, cuz I want the fish to know I
will kick you in YOUR FACE. I'M GOING TO
>> [laughter]
>> AND I WAS OUT THERE AND I'M SWIMMING AND
I'M HAVING A GREAT TIME, RIGHT? And all
of a sudden, there's these people and
they're playing WITH SOMETHING. SO, I
swim over there I said, "What are y'all
playing with?"
And they said a shark. I SAID, "OH OH OH
OKAY." [laughter]
I SAID, "LET ME LET YOU PLAY WITH YOUR
FRIEND." SHE SAYS, "NO no no, it's a
nurse shark, AND NURSE SHARKS DON'T
BITE." AND I'M THINKING, "HOW DO YOU
KNOW THAT THIS IS A NURSE?
WHAT IF IT IS A DOCTOR?
HE GOT TO BITE YOU CUZ YOU DISRESPECTED
HIS EDUCATION.
SO, I'M GETTING READY TO GET OUT THE
WATER, you know? And then another lady
said, "No no no no no. No no no." She
said, "Now you know what to do if a
shark comes too close to you." AND I'M
THINKING, "RUN?"
>> [laughter]
>> OH YEAH, CUZ JESUS WALKED ON WATER, BUT
I'M A HIGH KNEES IT UP OUT OF THERE.
>> [laughter]
>> AND SHE SAID SHE SAID, "NO SHE SAID IF A
SHARK COMES TOO close to you, you know
what you're supposed to do." Does
anybody know what you're supposed to do?
Look, they gave it only to THE WHITE
PEOPLE.
>> [laughter]
>> THEY DIDN'T TELL BLACK PEOPLE THAT AT
ALL.
>> [laughter]
>> ALL THE WHITE PEOPLE SAID, "PUNCH HIM IN
THE FACE."
DO I LOOK AUSTRALIAN TO YOU?
>> [laughter]
>> WHAT AM I SUPPOSED TO CHANNEL MY INNER
AUSSIE? "OI, ROY."
"CRIKEY."
>> [laughter]
>> "I'M GOING TO PUNCH HIM IN THE FACE. OI,
YEAH BOY."
"RIGHT IN FRONT OF YOUR MATES. RIGHT IN
THE KISSER." [laughter]
BUT DO YOU KNOW HOW SLOW YOU PUNCH
UNDERWATER?
>> [laughter]
>> IT'S NOT LIKE IT'S MORE LIKE "OOH."
THE shark's like, "You know I'm going to
bite THAT OFF, RIGHT?"
>> [laughter]
>> SO, I'M GETTING READY TO GET OUT OF THE
WATER, RIGHT? And I'm like, "Man, I'm
getting out." This man says, "No, no,
Jaylen. Jaylen." He said, "They just
trying to scare you."
And I'm like, "And what?"
>> [laughter]
>> He said, "As long as you don't do one
thing in the water." And I'm like,
"What is that? Be in the water?"
>> [laughter]
>> He says, "No." He says, "As long as you
don't pee IN THE WATER."
>> [laughter]
>> "YOU WON'T GET BIT by a shark."
Now, let me ask you something.
>> [laughter]
>> You look real smart.
If you see a shark
IN THE WATER,
>> [laughter]
>> CHANCES ARE
YOU DONE ALREADY PEED IN THE WATER.
>> [laughter]
>> AND IF YOU WANT TO BE HONEST, A LITTLE
BIT OF DOO-DOO CAME OUT, RIGHT?
DON'T GO OVER THERE.
>> [laughter]
>> WHERE'S THE BLUE STUFF? WHERE'S THE BLUE
STUFF?
>> [laughter]